SKILLS

English C1-C2 C

C# Python

JavaScript TypeScript

ASP.NET MVC

Angular Blazor

React TSQL

Azure Azure ML

MANUEL OSORIO

Electronic engineer, Web developer

PROFILE

Electronic engineer, studying a master's degree in Mechatronics and Automation. Programming since High School, currently focusing on C# .Net Framework (ASP.NET Core, Entity Framework, Identity, MVC, Blazor, etc) and integration with front-end technologies (Angular, React, JS). Great communication skills, self-learner, working experience with international teams and customer relationship management.

PROJECTS

Contributor

2023 - Current

TheCSharpAcademy

Web Apps creation, contributions to community projects, repository managment and code reviews in Github, etc.

EXPERIENCE

DWDM Product Manager

2021 - 2023

Huawei

Design of DWDM network solutions to different Latin American carriers, participation in RFP and RFQ for different companies, automation of internal processes for the creation of proposals and quotations, among others.

Assistant Professor

2019 - 2021

Department of mathematics

In charge of providing assistance to professors in the department of mathematics at the school of engineering. Grade assignments, test supervisor, creating support material, among other related works.

IT internship

2015

Social Welfare Ministry

EDUCATION

Mechatronics automation Engineering and Management

2023 -

Kun Shan University

Focusing on software automation and Machine Learning

Bachelor of science in electronics engineering

2016 - 2022

University of San Carlos of Guatemala

Degree with emphasis in telecommunications and embedded systems. Overall GPA of 3.3 (average grade of 87%).

AWARDS

Certification of training HCIP-Transmission

2022

Huawei Guatemala

Excellent intern award

2021

Huawei Guatemala

Academic Excellence Award (2020 - 2017)

2017-2020

USAC

CONTACT

- ·502 47870807
- aux.manuel.osorio@gmail.com
- Github
- in LinkedIn
- Portfolio